kwiksurveys.com 2017-03-09

# KwikSurveys: Free online survey & questionnaire tool

  * Home

  * Getting Started
    * Dashboard
    * Logic
      * Page Logic
      * Question Logic
      * Qualification Questions
    * Answer Randomization
    * Automatic Numbering
    * Locked Questions

  * Collaborate & Share

  * Reports Overview
    * Charting
    * Filtering
    * Comparisons
    * Individual results
    * Exporting data

  * Distributing
    * Address Book
    * Survey Distribution
    * Quick Poll Distribution
    * Spam Policy

  * Billing

  * Privacy Policy

  * Terms of Service

  * Contact Us

## 1\. Scope of the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy includes how Problem Free Limited (“Problem Free”), who created and operate www.kwiksurveys.com (“the Site”), treats personal information or data that Problem Free gathers when you are on the Site and when you use the Site’s services (“the Services”), whether that use be directly on the Site or a user of the Site utilising the Services to communicate with you. By using the Site and its Services, you agree to by bound by this Privacy Policy. Problem Free takes your privacy seriously and have fundamental guidelines that will be followed at all time:

  * We do not store your personal data, unless required to undertake the Services;
  * We do not disclose or sell your personal information to any third-party, unless we are required to do so by law or to protect our rights;
  * We do not require you to disclose personal information to us unless truly necessary to undertake the Services;
  * We shall keep your data on a secure server;
  * We shall allow you to control what information is public and what is kept private;
  * We shall undertake all reasonable and lawful requests to delete or correct your data.

## 2\. Personal Information

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. Problem Free may collect personally identifying information during the registration process, including name, email address, address, store preferences, billing information (see section on “Billing Information” below) etc. Problem Free reserves the right to track IP addresses of its users.  
You can object to our use of your personal information, however by doing so may prevent us from providing you with the Services. Users of our Site and Services may upload your personal information onto our site. All data is kept on our secure servers. Only Problem Free and the people who upload that information have access to that personal data.

## 3\. Disclosure of your Personal Information

Problem Free discloses your personal information only to employees, contractors and partner companies, but only where: * Disclosure of your personal information is required to perform the Services; and * The party receiving your information has agreed to keep it confidential.

All personal information is kept confidential unless required to do so by law, such as a court order or subpoena, or to protect Problem Free’s rights. Problem Free shall never sell your personal information to a third party or otherwise. Problem Free also may, on occasion, collect user preference information (such as items clicked from emails). We may also store information users knowingly and willingly provide such as feedback forms, suggestions, and emails to the Problem Free website. Problem Free may use such information for its internal purposes, including, but not limited to, email and web design optimizations, new features, and editorial and feedback purposes. Problem Free may send you emails to let you know about our newest and best deals available on the Site. If you are unhappy about receiving these, you can unsubscribe. To unsubscribe, click on the unsubscribe link in any Problem Free email. You will be taken to a confirmation page. Click on the confirm link and you will be unsubscribed. Problem Free shall take all reasonable measures to protect your data against theft, use, unauthorized use, unauthorized alteration and destruction.

## 4\. Anonymous Information

Problem Free may also, on occasion, collect user preference information (such as items clicked from emails). We may also store information users knowingly and willingly provide such as feedback forms, suggestions, and emails to the Problem Free website. Problem Free may use such information for its internal purposes, including, but not limited to, email and web design optimizations, new features, and editorial and feedback purposes. Like most websites we may collect anonymous information about you, made available by web browsers and servers, such as browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. None of this data is personally identifiable to you. This data may then be aggregated across all users in order to determine and target demographics for marketing and advertising purposes. All user information stored by Problem Free is considered confidential and will not be shared with outside parties except as described herein. Problem Free may share aggregated results of preferences for all users for marketing and advertising purposes, however these shall be anonymous.

## 5\. Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Problem Free cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is. Problem Free also uses a Google Analytics cookie to collect information about your use of the Site in order to optimise our users’ experience and use of the Services. Visitors can opt out of the Google Analytics features by using the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on available here. The "help" portion of the toolbar on many browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Problem Free's most attractive features.

## 6\. Security

Your Site account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.

## 7\. Billing Information

Problem Free uses a third party payment gateway to collect, store and process billing information. Problem Free does not store this information on its Site or servers. All payment pages use SSL technology.

## 8\. Transfer

If Problem Free, or any assets it owned, were acquired, or Problem Free went out of business, your personal information may be considered an asset and could be transferred to a third party (“the Transfer”). By using the Site and Services and therefore agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you agree that in the event of a Transfer that the third party receiving your personal information may continue to use the data as set out herein.

## 9\. Modifications to the Privacy Policy

Problem Free reserves the right to change this policy from time to time, however, all changes will be posted to this Privacy Policy at the time such changes are made. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page so please check back. Please note that continued access of Problem Free will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

If you have concerns or questions about any aspect of the Problem Free Privacy Policy, please e-mail us. We welcome your questions and feedback. Please send all emails to: support@problemfree.co.uk.
